

CONTACT INFO

- 1086-A, Sector- 41/B Chandigarh, India
- b43kd00r@gmail.com
- +919915517928
- https://b43kd00r.ninja

SKILLS SUMMARY

- •••• Web Application & API Penetration Testing
- ••• Network VA/PT
- Android & iOS ApplicationTesting
- Thick Client PenetrationTesting
- Security Automation, Kali
 Linux, Burp Suite, MobSF
- •••• Internal/External Infrastructure
 Penetration Testing

AWARDS RECEIVED

- eLearnSecurity WebApplication Penetration TestereXtreme eWPTXv2
- Certificate of Appreciation from NITTTR Chandigarh For Conducting Lab Sessions On "Web Application Security Audit" "Cyber Security" & Cyber Crime and Forensic"

RACHIT VERMA

APPLICATION SECURITY RESEARCHER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a seasoned Application Security Researcher with 1.7+ years of industry experience and a wealth of knowledge in the field of cybersecurity, acquired through 5+ years of participating in bug bounties. My expertise has been recognized by over 100 organizations worldwide, including Microsoft, Apple, Sony, Zomato, Intel and government entities such as the Government of New Zealand, CERT EU & Dutch NL and many more.

WORK EXPERIENCE

C-DAC, Hyderabad

Project Engineer - ISS | Aug 2021 - Present

- Proficient in executing internal and external Vulnerability
 Assessment and Penetration Testing (VAPT) activities with a
 strong track record of detailed documentation of identified
 vulnerabilities and remediation techniques.
- Experienced in investigating security breaches and other cyber security incidents, with on-site experience as an Information Security Service Provider (ISSP) for clients such as SBI, ONGC, PNB, Powergrid, BOI, and others. Proven ability to lower the risk by providing clients with security best practices and contributing to both delivery and practice units of the organization as a member of NAAT (NSCS).

WORK EXPERIENCE

C-DAC, Hyderabad

Security Researcher Intern | Jan 2021 - June 2021

- Experienced in classifying data on the dark web and identifying security vulnerabilities, with a goal to assess various vulnerabilities across dark web websites.
- Involved in developing a framework to identify, classify content and support forensic works to assist LEA India. A strong focus on finding and mitigating vulnerabilities to enhance the overall security posture.

EDUCATION

Chandigarh Engineering College, Mohali, Landran - Degree

AUG 2018 - JUNE 2021 | Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech) - Computer Science And Engineering (80.4%)

Chandigarh College Of Engg And Tech (CCET), Chandigarh - Diploma

AUG 2015 - JUNE 2018 | Computer Science And Engineering (73.7%) - Present

RESEARCH PAPERS

A Review Of Web Application Security Risks: Auditing And Assessment Of The Dark Web - IEEE

https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/9591031

INTEREST

Web3, OSINT And Bug Bounty